Guide to the Central Washington University Office of Alumni Relations, Memorabilia 1890s-2005
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Office of Alumni Relations, Memorabilia
1890s-2005
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG067b
Central Washington University Alumni Association
94 linear feet 43 boxes
The Alumni Relations Memorabilia collection features a variety of trophies, athletics gear, ceramics, glassware, clothing, and other items representative of Central Washington University’s history from the 1890s to 2013.
Textiles, commemorative objects, trophies, plaques, metal objects, athletics gear, and glassware in fair condition, with aging to older materials
Historical Note
The doors of the Washington State Normal School in Ellensburg opened in 1891. Mr. Benjamin Franklin Barge was the first principal of the school, which was founded to educate future elementary and junior high teachers. Classes were held at the Washington Public School until the normal school's first building, Barge Hall, opened in 1893. The normal school became Central Washington College of Education in 1937, Central Washington State College in 1961, and Central Washington University in 1977.
Founded in 1944, Central Washington University's Alumni Association provides opportunities for the continued connection between alumni and Central Washington University. The Alumni Association manages events and activities throughout the year, including reunions, homecoming, annual fundraising, Alumni Association scholarships and Distinguished Alumni Awards, Board meetings and workshops, the Central advisor program, tennis clinics, and miscellaneous gatherings.
The Alumni Relations collection features a variety of trophies, athletics gear, glassware, clothing, and other items representative of Central Washington University’s history from the 1890s to 2013. Notable are athletics items, including signed Dan Murphy and Dave Heaverlo jerseys.
Items will be added to series as accessioned
Open to the public for educational research
Materials related to the Alumni Relations collection may be found in the Athletic Department—-Team Sports collection. The athletics collection should be consulted for specifics about athletes and competitions.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University Alumni Association
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Alumni and alumnae
Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- 2 gold “Baseball Bat” ball display stands, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-004 (a and b) (Box 1)
  Three baseball bats with handles brought together
- 2 “Gold” trophies: “1997 CWU Alumni Board of Directors ‘Best Performance by a Volunteer’”, 067-06-73-005 (a and b) (Box 1)
  Faux marble plastic pedestal, 7.5L x 3.75W x 3.25 deep
- 1 wood plaque with metal: “National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics, National Championship, Men’s Basketball, March 14-20, 1989, District 1 Champion”, 067-06-73-006 (Box 1)
  8.5L x 8.5W x .75” deep
- 1 wood plaque with metal: “Monday Morning Quarterbacks Club, 1988 Fred Redmon Highest Honors Award, C.W.U. NAIA Womens Basketball Team”, 067-06-73-007 (Box 1)
  7L x 5W x .75” deep
- 1 wood plaque with metal: “1985-1986 Female Team of the Year”, 067-06-73-008 (Box 1)
  8L x 10W x .75” deep
- 1 wood plaque with metal: “Monday Morning Quarterbacks Club, 1985 Male Team of the Year, Central Washington University Men’s Basketball, Coach Dean Nicholson”, 067-06-73-009 (Box 1)
- 1 burnished gold cup trophy: “Evergreen Conference Champions, 1972”, 067-06-73-012 (Box 1)
  10.5L x 7.5W x 4.25” deep
- 1 wood plaque with metal; “Central Washington State College Varsity Swimming Inspirational Award”, 1960-1969; 067-06-73-013 (Box 1)
  14L x 10W x 1.75” deep. Award winners on award: Roger Hertrich (1960), Duane Bangs (1961), Dan Wolfrom (1962), William Dendurent (1963), Gerald Malella (1964, 1965), Thomas L. Thomas and Jeffrey J. Tinius (1966), Jeffrey J. Tinius (1967), Mark Schlosser (1968), Steve Kramer and Mike Smithers (1969).
- 1 copper cup trophy with wood base: “Women’s Chariot Race, Sweecy Day, 1963”, 067-06-73-015 (Box 1)
  7L x 3.25W x 3” deep
- 1 burnished gold trophy: “First Place Ladies’ Chariot, Sweecy Day, 1962”, 067-06-73-016 (Box 1)
  10.5L x 4W x 4” deep
- 1 burnished gold trophy: “Mock Convention Parade of 1960—‘Munson Hall’”, 067-06-73-017 (Box 1)
  15L x 5.5W x 4.5” deep
- 1 burnished gold cup trophy: “3rd Place, Freshman Activities, Munson Hall, 1960.” Plastic base., 067-06-73-018 (Box 1)
  6L x 3W x 3” deep
- 1 burnished gold cup trophy: “1st Place Homecoming Parade, 1955”, 067-06-73-019 (Box 1)
  9.5L x 4.5W x 3.75” deep
- 1 burnished gold cup trophy; “2nd Place Float, 1954, Homecoming—Kennedy Hall”, 067-06-73-020 (Box 1)
  8L x 3.75W x 2.75” deep
- 1 burnished gold cup: “CWCE Stunt Nite, 1953, 1st [place]”, 067-06-73-021 (Box 1)
  8L x 5.25W x 2.5” deep
- 1 Burnished Gold Cup Trophy; “SGA Inter-Dormitory Choral Competition, Kamola Hall, 1949 and 1951”, 067-06-73-022 (Box 2)
  14L x 5W x 4.50” deep. Plastic base.
- 1 Silver Cup Trophy; “Tri-Normal Baseball Champions, 1929, Ellensburg”, 067-06-73-024 (Box 2)
  11.75 x 8W x 6” deep
- 1 “Gold” Award with Wood Frame; “1st Place Chariot Race”, 067-06-73-025 (Box 2)
  6.5L x 4.25W x 2.5” deep
- 1 Copper Cup Trophy (Box 2)
  6.75L x 5.5W x 3.25” deep
- 1 Miniature Plate on Stand, 067-06-73-026 (Box 2)
  2.5” wide x 4.5” high
- 1 “Silver” Collectible Bell with Pewter Medallion, 067-06-73-027 (Box 2)
  3.75L x 1.50W x 1.50” deep. Plastic bell with pewter insert of CWU crest. In original box: “Fort” maker.
- 1 Metal Collectible Key Chain with Pewter Medallion, 067-06-73-028 (Box 2)
  3.5L x 1.5W x 2/16” deep. Metal chain and clasp holding pewter insert of CWU crest. In original box: “Fort” maker.
- 1 Marble Collectible Paperweight with Pewter Medallion, 067-06-73-029 (Box 2)
  2L x 2W x 1.25” deep. White marble square with pewter CWU crest on top. In original box: “Fort” maker.
- 1 “Silver” Collectible Wine Opener with Pewter Medallion, 067-06-73-030 (Box 2)
  7.25L x 2.50W x 1.5” deep. Plastic wine opener with pewter insert of CWU crest. In original box: “Fort” maker.
- 1 Wood Plaque with Metal Plate and Medallion: “CWU Reunion of the Century, Honoring CWU graduates and the Men and Women of the Fifties, July 30 and 31, 1999.”, 067-06-73-031 (Box 2)
  11.5L x 6.75W x 1” deep
- 1 Wood Plaque with Metal Plate, 2001; 067-06-73-032 (Box 2)
  15L x 12W x 1” deep
- 1 Wood Placard with Metal Nameplate: “Robert E. McConnell”, circa 1931-1959; 067-06-73-033 (Box 2)
  8.5L x 1.25W x 1.25” deep. The desk nameplate of former C.W.C.E. President, Robert E. McConnell.
- 1 Kodak Vigilant Junior Six-20 Camera—Rochester, N.Y., circa 1940-1948; 067-06-73-039 (Box 2)
  Open: 6.5L x 3 3/4W x 5.5” deep; Closed: 6.5L x 3.75W x 2” deep. Kodet lens with fixed focus, Dak shutter, folding bellows.
- 1 Pair of “Airguide” Achromatic 5 X 40 47A Binoculars, 067-06-73-040 (Box 2)
  5L x 4.5W x 1.75” deep. Eyepiece says “Airguide / Chicago U.S.A.”
- 1 “Humboldt Co.” Bunsen Burner (Metal), 067-06-73-041 (Box 2)
  7.5L x 3"W
- 1 Microscope with 48mm lens and removable black baseplate, 067-06-73-042 (Box 2)
  Lens says “Bausch & Lomb.” Serial Number: “State of Wash. 17008 C.W.C.E.”
- 1 Enamel / Metal? Measuring cup, 067-06-73-043 (Box 2)
  4L x 3W x 1.75” deep. Mark on bottom says “Coors USA 2.”
- 1 Wood Pedestal and Basketball, 067-06-73-047 (Box 3)
  6L x 6W x 6” deep. Pedestal held signed basketball for the “1997-1998 NAIA Men’s National Tournament Champions.” Basketball has signatures and jersey numbers of team.
- 1 Wood Pedestal for Basketball, 067-06-73-048 (Box 3)
  6L x 6W x 6” deep. Pedestal held signed basketball for the “500 Victories” ball of Coach Dean Nicholson. Basketball has signatures and jersey numbers of team.
- 1 Steel / Wood Discus, 067-06-73-049 (Box 3)
  7.5” diameter x 2 ¼“ deep. Made in Sweden.
- 1 Copper Printing Plate on Wood Block, circa 1890s-1910s; 067-06-73-050 (Box 3)
  4.25L x 3.25W x 1” deep
- 1 Copper Printing Plate on Wood Block, circa 1890s-1910s; 067-06-73-051 (Box 3)
  6L x 5W x 1.25” deep
- 1 Copper Printing Plate, 067-06-73-052 (Box 3)
  6.25L x 7.5W x 0.25” deep
- 1 Copper Printing Plate, 067-06-73-053 (Box 3)
  7L x 5W x 0.25” deep. Copper plate of Barge Hall.
- 1 Copper Printing Plate on Wood Block, circa 1890s-1910s; 067-06-73-054 (Box 3)
  7.25L x 6.25W x 1” deep
- 3 pairs of cleats, 067-06-73-055 (Box 4)
  12L x 7H x 5”W
- 1 hightop pair, brown/olive green, 067-06-73-056 (Box 4)
  11L x 6H x 4”W
- 1 pair of running shoes(?), circa 1920s-1940s; 067-06-73-057 (Box 4)
  10L x 4.5H x 3.5”W
- 1 pair MacGregor Knee Sheilds, Baseball?, 067-06-73-058 (Box 4)
  7.5L x 4.5”W. Embossed on one pad: “MacGregor Goldsmith Reg. U.S. Pat. Off., Made in U.S.A. 62”
- 1 Catcher’s Face Mask, 067-06-73-059 (Box 4)
  9L x 7.25W x 3.75” deep
- 1 Leather Case with Strap, 067-06-73-060 (Box 4)
  5.25L x 5.25W x 3” deep. This case may go with the binoculars that are also part of this collection. (See 067-06-73-060).
- 1 Spalding, two-tone leather football helmet with cloth jaw strap, circa 1930s-1950s; 067-06-73-061 (Box 5)
  9.5L x 8W x 11”H. Inside of helmet are the numbers “74-73.”
- 1 Leather Football “Glory” [Display] Helmet, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-062 (Box 5)
  10 ¼” L x 8.5” W x 7“ deep
- 1 Soft “D & M” Helmet with cloth strap, dark brown, circa 1920s-1940s; 067-06-73-064 (Box 6)
  13.5L x 12W x 2.5” deep
- 1 Leather Football Helmet, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-065 (Box 6)
  9.5L x 10W x 9” deep. Faint ink writing: “Bronk.” Manufactured by “Stall and Dean—Chicago.”
- 1 “Glory Helmet”, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-066 (Box 6)
  6L x 4.25W x 5.75” deep. Brown memorabilia helmet in 1/3 size of other helmets.
- 1 Spalding Baseball Glove, 067-06-73-067 (Box 6)
  9.5L x 10W x 2” deep
- 1 Spalding Catcher’s Mitt, 067-06-73-068 (Box 6)
  9L x 11.5W x 3.25” deep. Mitt is labeled with the numbers 123, the Spalding trademark, and the words “Professional Model” and “Hinged Pad.”
- 1 Signed Football, 067-06-73-069 (Box 7)
  Circa 2000 Baden football, signed by the team of the 1946 Championship team. Has stick-on letters: “CWCE 1946 Champions.”
- 1 Signed Football: Dan or Don Murphy, #35, 067-06-73-070 (Box 7)
  Wilson “College Football,” brown and white
- 1 Signed Football: Bob Osgood, 067-06-73-071 (Box 7)
  Encased in a plastic rectangle (11.5L x 8W x 6“ deep)
- 1 Signed Football, 2000; 067-06-73-072 (Box 7)
  Wilson “1005” football, brown
- 1 Signed Football, GNAC Champions / NCAA National Playoffs, 2002; 067-06-73-073 (Box 8)
  Baden football, brown and white. Lists regular season wins (11-0) and “Cascade Cup” score.
- 1 Signed Football, GNAC Champions / NCAA Playoffs, 2002; 067-06-73-074 (Box 8)
  Baden football; brown and white
- 1 Signed Volleyball, 1990s-2005; 067-06-73-075 (Box 9)
  Coach Mario Andaya signed, as well as players (jersey numbers also provided) in black marker
- 1 Signed Baseball (Encased), 067-06-73-076 (Box 9)
  Baseball is encased in a plastic pedestal (4.5L x 3.75W x 3.75“ deep)
- 1 Signed Baseball, 067-06-73-077 (Box 9)
  Ball has the signature of Dave Heaverlo
- 1 Signed Baseball, 067-06-73-078 (Box 9)
  Signature could be that of Bill North
- 1 Signed Softball, 2001; 067-06-73-079 (Box 9)
  Written on ball in black ink: “500th Career Coaching Victory at CWU”
- 1 Signed Basketball, 1987; 067-06-73-080 (Box 10)
  9 x 9". Basketball has stuck-on letters that read: “500 Victories / Dean Nicholson, 1964-1987.” Signed by players. (There is also a wood pedestal in the collection that was made to hold this ball. See 067-06-73-047.)
- 1 Signed Basketball (has wood pedestal), 1998; 067-06-73-081 (Box 11)
  9 x 9". Signed by the “NAIA Central Washington University 1997-1998 Men’s National Championship Tournament Team.”
- 1 CWU scarf, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-086 (Box 12)
- 1 CWU puff-ball knit hat, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-087 (Box 12)
- 1 baby sweater, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-088 (Box 12)
- 1 cheerleader top, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-089 (Box 12)
- 1 cheerleader skirt, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-090 (Box 12)
- 1 cheerleader skirt, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-091 (Box 12)
- 1 cheerleader skirt, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-092 (Box 12)
- 1 cheerleader sweater, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-093 (Box 12)
- 1 cheerleader sweater, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-094 (Box 12)
- 1 sweatshirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-095 (Box 13)
  24L x 22”W. White, long-sleeved sweatshirt with a design of McConnell Hall and below it: “Alumni Association Staff C.W.U.”
- 1 sweatshirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-096 (Box 13)
- 1 sweatshirt, 1995; 067-06-73-097 (Box 13)
  24L x 26”W. On the front is a laurel wreath with “Central Washington University, National Football Champions, NAIA Division II National Champions, 1995.”
- 1 sweatshirt, 1995; 067-06-73-098 (Box 13)
  30L x 29”W. Grey with burgundy and black design on front: “National Champions 1995 Central Washington Football.”
- 1 sweatshirt, 1998; 067-06-73-099 (Box 13)
  30L x 29”W. Grey with red and black design on top front: “1998 Central Washington University Columbia Football Association League Champions / Wildcats.”
- 1 sweatshirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-100 (Box 13)
  27L x 21.5”W. Tag inside reads: “Thelma’s Things (LaCrosse, Washington).
- 1 sweatshirt, circa 2000; 067-06-73-101 (Box 13)
  30L x 36”W. Red sweatshirt with “Battle for Seattle” design for football game of Central v. Western Washington University.
- 1 long-sleeved button-up shirt, 067-06-73-102 (Box 14)
  34L x 30”W. Embroidered on shirt is Barge Hall and the words: “Central Washington University Alumni Association.”
- 1 long-sleeved button-up shirt, 067-06-73-103 (Box 14)
  34L x 30”W. Denim blue shirt with collar and brown / tan buttons. Embroidered on it is part of Barge Hall and the words: “Central Washington University Alumni Association.”
- 1 long-sleeved T-shirt, 2000; 067-06-73-104 (Box 14)
  30L x 22”W. White shirt, for a “Homecoming Weekend 5K Fun Run / CWUWildcats.com.”
- 1 long-sleeved T-shirt, 1990s-2000s; 067-06-73-105 (Box 14)
  30L x 25”W. For “JAIA Men’s Basketball National Championship / Tulsa, Oklahoma.”
- 1 long-sleeved polo shirt, 1990s; 067-06-73-106 (Box 14)
  31L x 29”W. Red and white rugby striped polo with a black paw design and “SAC / CWU” overlaid in embroidery.
- 1 polo shirt, 067-06-73-107 (Box 14)
  27L x 20.5”W. White with a small Wildcat logo with “Wildcats CWU Alumni Association / Board of Directors.”
- 1 short-sleeved polo shirt, 067-06-73-108 (Box 14)
  32L x 24”W. Black with embroidered wildcat head and CWU above it.
- 1 short-sleeved polo shirt, 067-06-73-109 (Box 14)
  30L x 21”W. White with small design of fire truck “The General” and the words “CWU Alumni Association ‘The General’ Crew.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 067-06-73-110 (Box 14)
  22L x 20”W. Black with “Washington State Normal School” logo and a drawing of Barge Hall.
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-111 (Box 14)
  32L x 27.5”W. Brown and grey thin-striped shirt with yellow, green and blue design of four square blocks and “CWU / Central” overlaid.
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1991; 067-06-73-112 (Box 14)
  30L x 20.5”W. Grey with white and navy blue design of a dragon within a circle, a “C,” “91,” and “Central.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1991; 067-06-73-113 (Box 14)
  29L x 20.5”W. Red with black writing: “1891-1991 Centennial / Central Washington University Homecoming 1991.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1995; 067-06-73-114 (Box 14)
  28L x 21”W. The shirt reads: “Central Washington National Champions 1995.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1995; 067-06-73-115 (Box 14)
  29L x 21.5”W. The shirt reads: “Central Washington National Champions 1995.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1998; 067-06-73-116 (Box 14)
  31L x 25”W. Grey with red and black design on top front: “1998 Central Washington University Columbia Football Association League Champions / Wildcats.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1999; 067-06-73-117 (Box 14)
  31L x 25”W. White with blue, black and red design: “NCAA Basketball Men’s Division II Championship / Elite Eight / Louisville ’99!’”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 2000; 067-06-73-118 (Box 14)
  31L x 25”W. Grey with red and black design: “Road to Louisville / NCAA Elite Eight / Louisville 2000 / Division II Men’s Basketball.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 2000; 067-06-73-119 (Box 14)
  30L x 25”W. Grey with red and black design: “Road to Louisville / NCAA Elite Eight / Louisville 2000 / Division II Men’s Basketball.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 2000; 067-06-73-120 (Box 15)
  31L x 25”W. Blue with “Central Washington University, 2000 / The Future Is Here…Imagine It.”
- Grey T-shirt with brown, green and black design of hands, human head and chimp head, 067-06-73-121 (Box 15)
  25L x 20”W. Words surrounding the design say, “Central Washington University / Chimpanzee and Human / Washoe / Tatu / Dar / Moja / Loulis / Communication Institute.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 067-06-73-122 (Box 15)
  29L x 27”W. Aquamarine blue T-shirt with fish design and words: “Deep Sea Daze / CWU Dining Services.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1987; 067-06-73-123 (Box 15)
  27L x 18”W. “The 21st Annual Wild Boar Dinner / March 5, 1987 / CWU Dining Services” in white.
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1988; 067-06-73-124 (Box 15)
  28L x 21”W. “The 22nd Annual Wild Boar Dinner / March 3, 1988 / CWU Dining Services.”
- 1 short-sleeved T-shirt, 1990; 067-06-73-125 (Box 15)
  28L x 20.5”W. Aquamarine T-shirt with a boar wearing a checkered bib in black and pink writing: “March 1, 1990 / The 24th Annual Wild Boar Dinner / CWU Dining Services.”
- 1 short-sleeved women’s basketball warm-up T-shirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-126 (Box 15)
  30L x 23”W. White, mock turtleneck.
- 1 short-sleeved women’s basketball warm-up T-shirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-127 (Box 15)
  30L x 23”W. Embroidered “C” on the neck and embroidered “Wildcats” with basketball swishing through a net. Embroidered “Kristy” below net.
- 1 short-sleeved women’s basketball warm-up T-shirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-128 (Box 15)
  28L x 28”W. Black, mock turtleneck.
- 1 short-sleeved women’s basketball warm-up T-shirt, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-129 (Box 15)
- 1 non-reversible practice penny, circa 1960s; 067-06-73-130 (Box 15)
  20L x 15W x .5” deep. Red with stitched-on, black felt “CWSC 23.” The 1966-1967 Hyakem yearbook has photos of the women’s basketball team wearing pennies during practice.
- 1 cotton handkerchief, 067-06-73-131 (Box 15)
  21”L x 21”W. Navy blue with white design of dots and flowers. “Oriental Trading Company.” Made in China.
- 1 cotton handkerchief, 067-06-73-132 (Box 15)
- 1 vinyl bag, 1990; 067-06-73-133 (Box 15)
  11.5”L x 15.25”W. Commemorative bag for NAIA “Golden Anniversary / Education Through Athletics / September 29-October 3, 1990 / Kansas City, Missouri.”
- 1 stuffed animal, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-134 (Box 15)
  16”L x 10.5”W x 4” deep. Black cat with a red CWU shirt and black hat.
- 1 stuffed animal, circa 1955; 067-06-73-134 (Box 15)
  10L x 9.50W x 5“ deep. Tan hound dog with brown spots and two red CWU metal buttons.One button reads, “I’m a Wildcat / Homecoming 1955” and the other reads, “1954 Central Homecoming / Comic Capers / Go Get ‘Em, Wildcats.”
- 1 baseball cap, 2000; 067-06-73-136 (Box 16)
  Tan cap made by “Gear for Sports.” 100% cotton. Embroidered design reads: “NCAA Elite Eight Louisville, 2000.”
- 1 CWU Wildcats Football Cap, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-137 (Box 16)
  Black baseball cap with burgundy button and lid. Embroidered design of a football and the words: “Central Washington Wildcats Football.”
- 1 CWU Wildcats football cap, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-138 (Box 16)
- 1 CWU Wildcats baseball cap, circa 2000; 067-06-73-139 (Box 16)
  Navy blue caps with embroidered design of a wildcat wearing a CWU T-shirt and saying, “I am a Wildcat!”
- 1 CWU Wildcats baseball cap, circa 2000; 067-06-73-140 (Box 16)
- 1 Central baseball cap, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-141 (Box 16)
  Bright red, raised embroidery on cap. Front reads: “C.E.N.T.R.A.L.”
- 1 Central baseball cap, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-142 (Box 16)
- 1 Central baseball cap, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-143 (Box 16)
  Grey wool and acrylic cap with burgundy bill and button.
- 1 Central baseball cap, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-144 (Box 16)
- 1 San Francisco Giants baseball cap, circa 2000; 067-06-73-145 (Box 16)
  Black cap with orange button on top and embroidered “SF” on front.
- 1 Oakland As baseball cap, 1972; 067-06-73-146 (Box 16)
  Kelly green cap with dark green under-bill and yellow bill. A white “A’s” embroidered on the cap front.
- 1 Oakland As baseball cap, 1972; 067-06-73-147 (Box 16)
- 1 signed San Francisco Giants baseball cap, 1965; 067-06-73-148 (Box 16)
  Embroidered “SF” in orange. Signature on cap, but too faded to make out name.
- 1 signed San Francisco Giants baseball cap, 1965; 067-06-73-149 (Box 16)
- 1 cotton freshman beanie, 1964; 067-06-73-150 (Box 16)
  With felt iron-on letters in white: “CWS”
- 1 cotton freshman beanie, 1965; 067-06-73-151 (Box 16)
  Beanie is black on front and red on back. Small white letter iron-on “CWS.”
- 1 marching band hat, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-152 (Box 17)
  See http://www.demoulin.com/company/history.htm
- 1 AACO footed teacup and saucer set, 067-06-73-226 (Box 18)
  Back of plate: “Michael Carl Brandt, 1975”
- 1 AACO footed teacup and saucer set, 067-06-73-227 (Box 18)
  Back of plate: “Ronald C. Brandt, 1975 & 1991”
- 1 Aynsley (John Aynsley II) bone china plate, England, 067-06-73-228 (Box 18)
  Back of plate: “Lia (Lucchesi) Mori, 1945”
- 1 Aynsley bone china demitasse pedestal cup and saucer set, England, circa 1891-1933; 067-06-73-229 (Box 18)
- 1 Aynsley bone china “Stratford” (?) footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1940; 067-06-73-230 (Box 18)
  White with garden gate scene and wildflowers, gold trim
- 1 Aynsley bone china corset teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930-1950; 067-06-73-231 (Box 18)
- 1 bluebird fine bone china footed teacup and saucer set, Canada, 067-06-73-232 (Box 18)
  Back of plate: “F. Norman, 1954 and Eva Savage (Eyres) 1951)”
- 1 W. Borland footed demitasse cup and saucer, Germany, 067-06-73-233 (Box 18)
  Note on saucer: “Marit (Thomas) Rhodes, 1970. Died in TWA Flight 800 on 7/17/2006.”
- 1 Caledonia fine china teacup and saucer, 067-06-73-234 (Box 18)
  Provenance unknown. White with gold trim, purple thistle.
- 1 Carson Crockery Co. cup and saucer set, France, for U.S. export, 067-06-73-235 (Box 18)
  “Decorated by Haviland; Limoges”
- 1 Clarence bone china, England, circa 1922-1964; 067-06-73-236 (Box 18)
  White with sprays of blue and pink flowers, gold trim
- 1 Crown Dorset fine bone china footed cup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-237 (Box 19)
  White, gold trim, pink roses
- 1 Crown Essex bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930s-1960s; 067-06-73-238 (Box 19)
  Back of plate: “Margaret Stiltner, 1941 & 1961”
- 1 Crown Prince bone china, “B.C. Dogwood” footed teacup, England, 067-06-73-239 (Box 19)
  White, gold trim, dogwood flower
- 1 Royal Windsor bone china saucer, England (Box 19)
  Back of plate: “Carol (Albert) Fosnick, 1932/1933”
- 1 Crown Staffordshire “Blue Bows” fine bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1949; 067-06-73-240 (Box 19)
  White with hand-painted peacock-blue ribbon and bows and pink roses over a transfer pattern
- 1 Colclough china footed teacup and saucer (set?), England, circa 1948-1954; 067-06-73-241 (Box 19)
  Cup pattern number is 6620. Plate has pattern number 6631.
- 1 Colclough china teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1948-1954; 067-06-73-242 (Box 19)